<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Interprocess Communication on My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Interprocess Communication on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Group Membership Overview</title>
      <link>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-a/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-a/</guid>
      <description>Overview  Jiffy-generated applications can be deployed as single or multiple instances. When running multiple instances of a Jiffy-generated application, a group-membership service is started inside each application instance. A group is defined as a set of application instances running the group-membership service. An application instance knows to start its group-membership service if the -gm flag is provided during startup. Each application instance running the group-membership service can be thought of as a process.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Failure Detector</title>
      <link>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-b/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-b/</guid>
      <description>Group Membership Failure Detector  When discussing deployment of a Jiffy-generated application, each instance of the application is referred to as a process. Processes may fail. Processes exist with one of three publicly disseminated and well-known statuses: {ACTIVE; SUSPECT; FAILED} Processes exist with a publicly (within the group) disseminated incarnation number. Process viability is checked at selectable intervals (ping-cycle time) via a ping-ack mechanism. Each process pings all other processes in the group once per ping-cycle in random order.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Access Revocation and Renewal</title>
      <link>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-c/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://1414c.github.io/jiffy/interprocess/ip-content-c/</guid>
      <description>JWT Tokens and Access Revocation Jiffy applications do not support the revocation or automatic renewal of JWT tokens. Instead, the service ensures that changes to User information (create/update/delete) are disseminated to all running instances of the Jiffy generated application. This is accomplished by maintaining a cross-process cache of User information via the group-membership service.
Consequently, in Jiffy-based applications it makes sense to discuss User access revocation from the perspective of an administrator making a call to the user-API to perform general User deletion or deactivation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>